<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Rekt News RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.rekt.news/</link><description>Latest news from Rekt News</description><item><title>Uwulend - Rekt</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//uwulend-rekt/</link><pubDate>Monday, June 10, 2024</pubDate><description>The velo in Velocore proved too fast and furious, as the L2 DEX lost over $6.8 million in a devastating exploit on June 2nd across its pools on Linea and zkSync.</description></item><item><title>Velocore - Rekt</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//velocore-rekt/</link><pubDate>Monday, June 3, 2024</pubDate><description>The velo in Velocore proved too fast and furious, as the L2 DEX lost over $6.8 million in a devastating exploit on June 2nd across its pools on Linea and zkSync.</description></item><item><title>DMM Bitcoin - Rekt</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//dmm-rekt/</link><pubDate>Friday, May 31, 2024</pubDate><description>Centralized Japanese crypto exchange DMM Bitcoin exploited for more than $304 million in Bitcoin. What could go down as one of the biggest heists in our industry, became another prime example of not your keys, not your crypto.</description></item><item><title>Meme Mania</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//meme-mania/</link><pubDate>Wednesday, May 29, 2024</pubDate><description>Fueled by unquenchable greed and feverish FOMO, degens are being lured into crypto's volatile wild west of meme coins, where mind-boggling gains and soul-crushing losses are always just one trade away.</description></item><item><title>Gala Games - Rekt</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//gala-games-rekt/</link><pubDate>Tuesday, May 21, 2024</pubDate><description>Possible hacker seized control of an admin address to mint a whopping 5 billion GALA tokens worth $216 million, rapidly offloading 592 million tokens for $21.8 million in ETH before Gala Games could blacklist the rogue address.</description></item><item><title>AlexLab - Rekt</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//alexlab-rekt/</link><pubDate>Friday, May 17, 2024</pubDate><description>AlexLab, the self-proclaimed finance layer on Bitcoin, had a few layers stripped, as a compromised private key led to a $4.3 million exploit on AlexLab’s XLink bridge on the BNB network.</description></item><item><title>Sonne Finance - Rekt</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//sonne-finance-rekt/</link><pubDate>Thursday, May 16, 2024</pubDate><description>The alarm has been rung on Sonne Finance, as a $20 million flash loan attack reverberates across the crypto sphere, chiming a somber melody that warns of the perils lurking in the DeFi shadows.</description></item><item><title>Crypto Under Siege</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//crypto-under-siege/</link><pubDate>Wednesday, May 15, 2024</pubDate><description>The recent assault on crypto has some fighting back, but some are running scared too. As the crypto market expands, U.S. agencies like the SEC, DOJ, and Treasury are cracking down on the industry with a regulations blitz, setting their sights on major crypto players.</description></item><item><title>Gamestonk II - Dumb Money is Back</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//gamestonk2/</link><pubDate>Tuesday, May 14, 2024</pubDate><description>GameStop meme frenzy went supernova once again, leaving a $1 billion trail of crater-faced short sellers in its wake.</description></item><item><title>Pike Finance - Rekt</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//pike-rekt/</link><pubDate>Friday, May 3, 2024</pubDate><description>Pike Finance swims in turbulent waters, storage vulnerability nets hackers over $1.9 million in multiple attacks.</description></item><item><title>Growing Pains</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//growing-pains/</link><pubDate>Wednesday, May 1, 2024</pubDate><description>Solana's relentless pursuit of speed and scalability has transformed the blockchain landscape. But at what cost?</description></item><item><title>ZKasino - Rekt</title><link>https://www.rekt.news//zkasino-rekt/</link><pubDate>Monday, April 22, 2024</pubDate><description>The house always wins and ZKasino hit the jackpot, making off with a $33 million rug over the weekend.</description></item></channel></rss>